yepads.com 2013-12-10

# Online classified ads bangalore, chennai, mumbai, India | Free online classified ads submission delhi, bangalore | post free ads in Bangalore, Chennai, Delhi, Mumbai, India.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which YepAds.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.yepads.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Idea Solutions.

**Personal Information**  
We may collect personal information from Users in a variety, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Web browser cookies**  
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies.

**How we use collected information**  
www.yepads.com may use Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To improve customer service.   
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To personalize user experience.  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.
  * To improve our Site.  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * To process payments.  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order.  
We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * To send periodic emails & sms.  
We may use the email address & mobile no to send updates / alerts. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

**How we protect your information**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access. Unfortunately no data over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Any information you provide, you do so at your own risk. We take appropriate steps to protect that from any loss misuse and unauthorised access. 

**Sharing your personal information**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. However user agree that by posting any personal information of themselves or any other person, are the sole responsibility of the user. Users agree and accept the terms of the Privacy Policy for use of any features on the site.

**Third party websites**  
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible. 

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
www.yepads.com may update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contact us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, Please contact us at:  
Email: [admin@yepads.com](mailto:admin@yepads.com)

This document was last updated on September 14, 2012
